Guide to the Howard E. Buswell papers and photographs 1822-1965
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Map Collection, undated; Series XV
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Fairhaven, 1889-1903 (Map-folder 21)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Georgia City, Glacier, Hollingsworth, Kendall Cemetery, Kingsborro, Lynden, 1871-1910 (Map-folder 22)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Lummi Island, Lummi Native American Reservation, 1874-1957 (Map-folder 23)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Maple Falls, Marietta, Millerton, Newport, Nooksack Village, Nooksack River, 1880-1941 (Map-folder 24)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Orchard Park, Pacific Orchard, Point Roberts, Plymouth City, Lake Samish, 1888-1913 (Map-folder 25)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Sehome, 1858-1905 (Map-folder 26)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Semiahmoo, Strandell, Sumas, 1873-1911 (Map-folder 27)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Wesley, Wickersham, Lake Whatcom, 1884-1909 (Map-folder 28)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Whatcom, 1858-1890 (Map-folder 29)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Whatcom, 1871-1904 (Map-folder 30)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Whatcom, 1871-1903 (Map-folder 31)
  - Whatcom County - Incorporated Areas - Various, 1871-1913 (Map-folder 32)
  - Township and Range Maps of Whatcom County, pages 1-30, 1889 (Map-folder 33)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 1-5, 1858 (Map-folder 34)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 6-15, 1871 (Map-folder 35)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 16-22, 1883 (Map-folder 36)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 23-32, 1883 (Map-folder 37)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 33-40, 1884 (Map-folder 38)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 41-45, 1885 (Map-folder 39)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 46-56, 1888 (Map-folder 40)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 57-68, 1888 (Map-folder 41)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 69-80, 1889 (Map-folder 42)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 81-90, 1889 (Map-folder 43)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. I, pages 91-99, 1889 (Map-folder 44)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 2-10, 1889 (Map-folder 45)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 11-18, 1889 (Map-folder 46)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 19-28, 1889 (Map-folder 47)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 29-35, 1889 (Map-folder 48)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 36-42, 1889 (Map-folder 49)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 43-50, 1889 (Map-folder 50)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 51-58, 1889 (Map-folder 51)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 59-68, 1889 (Map-folder 52)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 69-76, 1890 (Map-folder 53)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 77-84, 1890 (Map-folder 54)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 85-92, 1890 (Map-folder 55)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. II, pages 93-100, 1890 (Map-folder 56)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. III, pages 1-10, 1890 (Map-folder 57)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. III, pages 11-20, 1890 (Map-folder 58)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. III, pages 21-30, 1890 (Map-folder 59)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. III, pages 31-40, 1890 (Map-folder 60)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. III, pages 41-49, 1890 (Map-folder 61)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. IV, pages 2-10, 1891 (Map-folder 62)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. IV, pages 11-20, 1891 (Map-folder 63)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. IV, pages 21-29, 1891 (Map-folder 64)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. IV, pages 30-37, 1891 (Map-folder 65)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. IV, pages 38-50, 1891 (Map-folder 66)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. V, pages 1-10, 1892 (Map-folder 67)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. V, pages 11-21, 1898 (Map-folder 68)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. V, pages 22-30, 1900 (Map-folder 69)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. V, pages 31-40, 1903 (Map-folder 70)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. V, pages 41-50, 1907 (Map-folder 71)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. VI, pages 2-10, 1909 (Map-folder 72)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. VI, pages 11-21, 1911 (Map-folder 73)
  - Whatcom County Plats, Vol. VI, pages 22-30, 1913 (Map-folder 74)
- Photograph Collection, Series XVI
  To view item-level description of images in the Howard Buswell collection, follow
  this hyperlink to the photo catalog on the Center for Pacific Northwest Studies' website.